<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<!DOCTYPE xliff PUBLIC "-//XLIFF//DTD XLIFF//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/committees/xliff/documents/xliff.dtd">
<xliff version="1.0">
  <file source-language="EN" target-language="de" datatype="plaintext" original="sfForkedApply" date="2010-03-16T21:58:27Z" product-name="sfForkedApply">
    <header/>
    <body>
      <trans-unit id="1" approved="yes">
        <source>&lt;p&gt;
Thanks for applying for an account on %1%.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
To prevent abuse of the site, we require that you activate your account by clicking on the following link:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
%2%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Thanks again for joining us.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Danke für die Beantragung eines Accounts auf %1%.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Um Miissbrauch vorzubeugen, musst du deinen Account aktivieren. Klicke dazu einfach auf den folgenden Link:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
%2%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Danke für deine Registrierung.
&lt;/p&gt;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="2" approved="yes">
        <source>Continue</source>
        <target>Weiter</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="3" approved="yes">
        <source>&lt;p&gt;
That confirmation code is invalid.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
This may be because you have already confirmed your account. If so,
just click on the "Log In" button to log in.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Other possible explanations:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
1. If you copied and pasted the URL from
your confirmation email, please make sure you did so correctly and
completely.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
2. If you received this confirmation email a long time ago
and never confirmed your account, it is possible that your account has
been purged from the system. In that case, you should simply apply
for a new account.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Der Bestätigungs - Code ist ungültig.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Möglicherweise wurde dein Account bereits aktiviert. Sollte das der Fall sein, dann klicke auf "Login" und logge dich ein.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Andere Möglichkeiten:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
1. Wenn du den Link kopiert hast, vergewissere dich das dieser vollständig und korrekt kopiert wurde.
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
2. Wenn du dich bereits vor einiger Zeit registriert hast, ist es möglich das dein Account aus dem System entfernt wurde. Sollte das der Fall sein, erstelle einfach einen neuen Account.
&lt;/p&gt;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="4" approved="yes">
        <source>Apply for an Account</source>
        <target>Account Registrierung</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="5" approved="yes">
        <source>Create My Account</source>
        <target>Account erstellen</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="6" approved="yes">
        <source>or</source>
        <target>oder</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="7" approved="yes">
        <source>Cancel</source>
        <target>Abbrechen</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="8" approved="yes">
        <source>Forgot your username or password? No problem! Just enter your username &lt;strong&gt;or&lt;/strong&gt;
your email address and click "Reset My Password." You will receive an email message containing both your username and
a link permitting you to change your password if you wish.</source>
        <target>Du hast dein Usernamen oder dein Passwort vergessen? Kein Problem! Gib einfach deinen Usernamen &lt;strong&gt;oder&lt;/strong&gt; deine E-Mail Adresse an und klicke "Passwort zurücksetzen". Du erhälst dann eine E-Mail mit deinem Usernamen und einen Link der es dir ermöglicht dein Passwort zu ändern, wenn du das möchtest.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="9" approved="yes">
        <source>Reset My Password</source>
        <target>Passwort zurücksetzen</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="10" approved="yes">
        <source>Thanks for applying for an account with %1%.

To prevent abuse of the site, we require that you activate your account by clicking on the following link:

%2%

Thanks again for joining us.</source>
        <target>Danke für die Beantragung eines Accounts mit %1%.

Um Miissbrauch vorzubeugen, musst du deinen Account aktivieren. Klicke dazu einfach auf den folgenden Link:

%2%

Danke für deine Registrierung.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="11" approved="yes">
        <source>Your password has been successfully reset. You are now logged
in to this site. In the future, be sure to log in with your new password.</source>
        <target>Dein Passwort wurde erfolgreich zurückgesetzt. Du bist jetzt eingeloggt. Denke zukünftig daran, dich mit deinem neuen Passwort anzumelden.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="12" approved="yes">
        <source>Thanks for confirming your email address. You may now change your
password using the form below.</source>
        <target>Danke für die Bestätigung deiner E-Mail Adresse. Du kannst jetzt dein Passwort, mit dem unteren Formular, ändern.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="13" approved="yes">
        <source>&lt;p&gt;
For security reasons, a confirmation message has been sent to
the email address associated with this account. Please check your
email for that message. You will need to click on a link provided
in that email in order to change your password. If you do not see
the message, be sure to check your "spam" and "bulk" email folders.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
We apologize for the inconvenience.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Aus Sicherheitsgründen, wurde eine Bestätigung an die E-Mail Adresse dieses Accounts geschickt.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Wir entschuldigen uns für die Unannehmlichkeiten.
&lt;/p&gt;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="14" approved="yes">
        <source>
&lt;p&gt;
We have received your request to recover your username and possibly your password on: %1%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Your username is: %USERNAME%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
If you have lost your password or wish to reset it, click on the link that follows:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
%2%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
You will then be prompted for the new password you wish to use.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Your password will not be changed unless you click on the link above and complete the form.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Nous avons reçu votre demande de récupération d'identifiant et peut-être également de mot de passe sur %1%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Dein Username: %USERNAME%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Wenn du dein Passwort vergessen hast oder es zurücksetzen möchtest, dann klicke auf den folgenden Link:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
%2%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Du wirst aufgefordert dein neues Passwort anzugeben.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Dein Passwort wir nicht geändert, solange du nicht auf den oberen Link klickst und das Formular ausfüllst.
&lt;/p&gt;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="15" approved="yes">
        <source>&lt;p&gt;
An error took place during the email delivery process. Please try
again later.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Bei der E-Mail Übertragung ist ein Fehler aufgetreten. Versuche es später erneut.
&lt;/p&gt;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="16" approved="yes">
        <source>sign in</source>
        <target>Anmeldung</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="17" approved="yes">
        <source>Reset Your Password</source>
        <target>Passwort zurücksetzen</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="18" approved="yes">
        <source>Create a New Account</source>
        <target>Neuen Account erstellen</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="19" approved="yes">
        <source>Account Settings</source>
        <target>Account Einstellungen</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="20" approved="yes">
        <source>Save</source>
        <target>Speichern</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="21" approved="yes">
        <source>Click the button below to change your password.</source>
        <target>Klicke auf die untere Schaltfläche, um dein Passwort zu ändern.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="22" approved="yes">
        <source>Reset Password</source>
        <target>Passwort zurücksetzen</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="23" approved="yes">
        <source>Thank you for applying for an account. You will receive a verification
email shortly. If you do not see that email, please be sure to check your "spam" or "bulk" folder.</source>
        <target>Danke für die Beantragung eines Accounts. Du wirst in kürze eine Bestätigungs E-Mail erhalten. Solltest du diese E-Mail nicht sehen, überprüfe deinen Spam Ordner.
</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="24" approved="yes">
        <source>Sorry, there is no user with that username or email address.</source>
        <target>Es gibt keinen User mit diesem Usernamen oder dieser E-Mail Adresse.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="25" approved="yes">
        <source>
That account was never verified. You must verify the account before you can log in or, if
necessary, reset the password. We have resent your verification email, which contains
instructions to verify your account. If you do not see that email, please be sure to check
your "spam" or "bulk" folder.</source>
        <target>Dieser Account wurde nicht aktiviert. Du musst deinen Account aktivieren bevor du dich einloggen kannst, oder dein Passwort zurücksetzen. Wir haben dir eine Bestätigungs E-Mail geschickt, in der du eine Anleitung zur Account aktivierung findest. Solltest du diese E-Mail nicht sehen, überprüfe deinen Spam Ordner.
</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="26" approved="yes">
        <source>We have received your request to recover your username and possibly your password on:

%1%

Your username is: %USERNAME%

If you have lost your password or wish to reset it, click on the link that follows:

%2%

You will then be prompted for the new password you wish to use.

Your password will NOT be changed unless you click on the link above and complete the form.</source>
        <target>
Nous avons reçu votre demande de récupération d'identifiant et peut-être également de mot de passe sur %1%

Dein Username: %USERNAME%

Wenn du dein Passwort vergessen hast oder es zurücksetzen möchtest, dann klicke auf den folgenden Link:

%2%

Du wirst aufgefordert dein neues Passwort anzugeben.

Dein Passwort wir nicht geändert, solange du nicht auf den oberen Link klickst und das Formular ausfüllst.
</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="27" approved="yes">
        <source>Thank you for confirming your account! You are now logged into the site.</source>
        <target>Danke das du deinen Account aktiviert hast! Du bist jetzt eingeloggt.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="28" approved="yes">
        <source>&lt;p&gt;
This account is inactive. Please contact the administrator.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Dieser Account ist nicht aktiviert. Kontaktiere den Administrator.
&lt;/p&gt;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="29" approved="yes">
        <source>Logged in as %1%</source>
        <target>Eingeloggt als %1%</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="30" approved="yes">
        <source>Log Out</source>
        <target>Ausloggen</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="31" approved="yes">
        <source>Settings</source>
        <target>Einstellungen</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="32" approved="yes">
        <source>Please verify your account on %1%</source>
        <target>Bitte überprüfe deinen Account auf %1%</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="33" approved="yes">
        <source>Please verify your password reset request on %1%</source>
        <target>Bitte überprüfe dein Passwort, zurücksetzen auf %1%</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="34" approved="yes">
        <source>You may change your password using the form below.</source>
        <target>Du hast dein Passwort vielleicht nach der unteren Form formatiert.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="35" approved="yes">
        <source>The captcha is not valid (%error%).</source>
        <target>Captcha-Code ungültig (%error%).</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="36" approved="yes">
        <source>Unable to check the captcha from the server (%error%).</source>
        <target>Captcha-Code nicht verfügbar (%error%).</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="43" approved="yes">
        <source>For security reasons, you
will receive a confirmation email containing a link allowing you to complete the password change.</source>
        <target>Aus Sicherheitsgründen bekommst du eine Bestätigungs E-Mail, mit einem klick auf den Link ist die Passwortänderung abgeschlossen.</target>
      </trans-unit>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>

