<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<!DOCTYPE xliff PUBLIC "-//XLIFF//DTD XLIFF//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/committees/xliff/documents/xliff.dtd">
<xliff version="1.0">
  <file source-language="EN" target-language="pt" datatype="plaintext" original="sfForkedApply" date="2010-03-16T21:58:27Z" product-name="sfForkedApply">
    <header/>
    <body>
      <trans-unit id="1" approved="yes">
        <source>&lt;p&gt;
Thanks for applying for an account on %1%.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
To prevent abuse of the site, we require that you activate your account by clicking on the following link:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
%2%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Thanks again for joining us.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Obrigado por criar uma conta em %1%.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Para previnir abusos no site, exigimos que você ative sua conta clicando no link a seguir:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
%2%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Obrigado por juntar-se a nós.
&lt;/p&gt;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="2" approved="yes">
        <source>Continue</source>
        <target>Continuar</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="3" approved="yes">
        <source>&lt;p&gt;
That confirmation code is invalid.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
This may be because you have already confirmed your account. If so,
just click on the "Log In" button to log in.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Other possible explanations:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
1. If you copied and pasted the URL from
your confirmation email, please make sure you did so correctly and
completely.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
2. If you received this confirmation email a long time ago
and never confirmed your account, it is possible that your account has
been purged from the system. In that case, you should simply apply
for a new account.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Este código de confirmação é inválido.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Isto pode acontecer porquê você já confirmou a sua conta. Se for assim, acione "Acessar" para entrar.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Outras possibilidades:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
1. Se você copiou e colou a URL do e-mail de confirmação, assegure-se de tê-lo feito corratamente.
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
2. Se recebeu este e-mail de confirmação há algum tempo e não confirmou a sua conta, é possível que sua conta tenha sido eliminada do sistema. Neste caso, deve requerer um novo registro.
&lt;/p&gt;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="4" approved="yes">
        <source>Apply for an Account</source>
        <target>Registre-se</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="5" approved="yes">
        <source>Create My Account</source>
        <target>Criar nova conta</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="6" approved="yes">
        <source>or</source>
        <target>ou</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="7" approved="yes">
        <source>Cancel</source>
        <target>Cancelar</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="8" approved="yes">
        <source>Forgot your username or password? No problem! Just enter your username &lt;strong&gt;or&lt;/strong&gt;
your email address and click "Reset My Password." You will receive an email message containing both your username and
a link permitting you to change your password if you wish.</source>
        <target>Esqueceu sua senha? Não tem problema! Basta digitar seu nome de usuário &lt;strong&gt;ou&lt;/strong&gt;
seu endereço de e-mail e clique em "Reiniciar senha". Você receberá uma mensagem de e-mail contendo o seu nome de usuário e
um link que permitirá definir uma nova senha.
        </target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="9" approved="yes">
        <source>Reset My Password</source>
        <target>Reiniciar senha</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="10" approved="yes">
        <source>Thanks for applying for an account with %1%.

To prevent abuse of the site, we require that you activate your account by clicking on the following link:

%2%

Thanks again for joining us.</source>
        <target>Obrigado por registrar-se em %1%.

Para previnir abusos no site, exigimos que você ative sua conta clicando no link a seguir:

%2%

Obrigado por registrar-se.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="11" approved="yes">
        <source>Your password has been successfully reset. You are now logged
in to this site. In the future, be sure to log in with your new password.</source>
        <target>Sua senha foi reiniciada com sucesso. A partir de agora você pode ser autenticado pelo sistema. A partir de agora, acesse utilizando a NOVA senha.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="12" approved="yes">
        <source>Thanks for confirming your email address. You may now change your
password using the form below.</source>
        <target>Obrigado por confirmar seu e-mail. Agora deve trocar a sua senha usando o formulário seguinte.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="13" approved="yes">
        <source>&lt;p&gt;
For security reasons, a confirmation message has been sent to 
the email address associated with this account. Please check your
email for that message. You will need to click on a link provided
in that email in order to change your password. If you do not see
the message, be sure to check your "spam" and "bulk" email folders.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
We apologize for the inconvenience.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Por razões de segurança, uma mensagem de confirmação foi enviado para
o endereço de e-mail associado a essa conta. Por favor verifique o seu
e-mail para essa mensagem. Você precisará clicar em um link fornecido
no e-mail, a fim de alterar sua senha. Se você não localizar
a mensagem, não esqueça de verificar as pastas de "spam" e "mensagem não desejada".
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Pedimos desculpas pela inconveniência.
&lt;/p&gt;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="14" approved="yes">
        <source>
&lt;p&gt;
We have received your request to recover your username and possibly your password on: %1%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Your username is: %USERNAME%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
If you have lost your password or wish to reset it, click on the link that follows:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
%2%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
You will then be prompted for the new password you wish to use.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Your password will not be changed unless you click on the link above and complete the form.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Recebemos uam solicitação para recuperar seu usuário e possivelmente a sua senha em: %1%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Seu usuário: %USERNAME%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Se perdeu a sua senha ou queira reinicia-lá, acione o seguinte link:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
%2%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Em seguida, lhe será solicitado uma nova senha.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Sua senha não será alterada a menos que você clique no link acima e preencha o formulário.
&lt;/p&gt;
</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="15" approved="yes">
        <source>&lt;p&gt;
An error took place during the email delivery process. Please try
again later.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Um erro ocorreu durante o processo de envido do e-mail. Por favor, tente
mais tarde novamente.
&lt;/p&gt;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="16" approved="yes">
        <source>sign in</source>
        <target>Acessar</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="17" approved="yes">
        <source>Reset Your Password</source>
        <target>Reiniciar sua senha</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="18" approved="yes">
        <source>Create a New Account</source>
        <target>Criar uma nova conta</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="19" approved="yes">
        <source>Account Settings</source>
        <target>Preferências da conta</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="20" approved="yes">
        <source>Save</source>
        <target>Salvar</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="21" approved="yes">
        <source>Click the button below to change your password. For security reasons, you
will receive a confirmation email containing a link allowing you to complete the password change.</source>
        <target>Clique no botão abaixo para alterar sua senha. Por razões de segurança, você
receberá um email de confirmação contendo um link que lhe permite finalizar o processo.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="22" approved="yes">
        <source>Reset Password</source>
        <target>Reiniciar senha</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="23" approved="yes">
        <source>Thank you for applying for an account. You will receive a verification email shortly. If you do not see that email, please be sure to check your "spam" or "bulk" folder.</source>
        <target>Obrigado por registrar-se. Receberá uma e-mail de verificação em breve. Se você não localizar
a mensagem, não esqueça de verificar as pastas de "spam" e "mensagem não desejada"</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="24" approved="yes">
        <source>Sorry, there is no user with that username or email address.</source>
        <target>Desculpe, mas não existe nenhuma conta de usuário com este nome.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="25" approved="yes">
        <source>
That account was never verified. You must verify the account before you can log in or, if
necessary, reset the password. We have resent your verification email, which contains
instructions to verify your account. If you do not see that email, please be sure to check 
your "spam" or "bulk" folder.</source>
        <target>
Essa conta nunca foi confirmada. Você deve confirma-lá antes de entrar ou, se
necessário, redefinir a senha. Verifique o e-mail de confirmação, que contém
instruções de como fazê-lo. Se você não localizar este e-mail, por favor, não esqueça verifique as pastas
"spam" ou "mensagem não solicitadas".
        </target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="26" approved="yes">
        <source>We have received your request to recover your username and possibly your password on:

%1%

Your username is: %USERNAME%

If you have lost your password or wish to reset it, click on the link that follows:

%2%

You will then be prompted for the new password you wish to use.

Your password will NOT be changed unless you click on the link above and complete the form.
        </source>
        <target>Recebemos uma requisição para recuperar seu usuário e senha em:

%1%

Seu usuário: "%USERNAME%"

Se perdeu sua senha ou desenha reinicia-lá, acione o seguinte link:

%2%

Em seguida, lhe será solicita uma NOVA senha.

Sua senha NÃO será trocada a não ser que acione o link acima e complete o formulário.
        </target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="27" approved="yes">
        <source>Thank you for confirming your account! You are now logged into the site.</source>
        <target>Obrigado por confirma a sua conta. Agora você esta logado.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="28" approved="yes">
        <source>&lt;p&gt;
This account is inactive. Please contact the administrator.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Esta conta está inactiva. Por favor, entre em contato com o administrador.
&lt;/p&gt;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="29" approved="yes">
        <source>Logged in as %1%</source>
        <target>Conectado em %1%</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="30" approved="yes">
        <source>Log Out</source>
        <target>Desconectar</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="31" approved="yes">
        <source>Settings</source>
        <target>Configuração</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="32" approved="yes">
        <source>Please verify your account on %1%</source>
        <target>Por favor, verifica a sua conta em %1%</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="33" approved="yes">
        <source>Please verify your password reset request on %1%</source>
        <target>Por favor, verifique a sua requisição de reiniciar a senha em %1%</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="34" approved="yes">
        <source>You may change your password using the form below.</source>
        <target>Pode trocar a senha utilizando o seguinte formulário.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="35" approved="yes">
        <source>The captcha is not valid (%error%).</source>
        <target>Captcha inválido (%error%).</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="36" approved="yes">
        <source>Unable to check the captcha from the server (%error%).</source>
        <target>Imposivel verificar o captcha no servidor (%error%).</target>
      </trans-unit>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>
