<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<!DOCTYPE xliff PUBLIC "-//XLIFF//DTD XLIFF//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/committees/xliff/documents/xliff.dtd">
<xliff version="1.0">
  <file source-language="EN" target-language="it" datatype="plaintext" original="sfForkedApply" date="2010-03-16T21:58:27Z" product-name="sfForkedApply">
    <header/>
    <body>
      <trans-unit id="1" approved="yes">
        <source>&lt;p&gt;
Thanks for applying for an account on %1%.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
To prevent abuse of the site, we require that you activate your account by clicking on the following link:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
%2%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Thanks again for joining us.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Grazie per aver creato un account su %1%.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Per prevenire abusi sul sito, noi richiediamo che tu attivi il tuo account cliccando sul seguente link:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
%2%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Grazie ancora per esserti registrato.
&lt;/p&gt;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="2" approved="yes">
        <source>Continue</source>
        <target>Prosegui</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="3" approved="yes">
        <source>&lt;p&gt;
That confirmation code is invalid.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
This may be because you have already confirmed your account. If so,
just click on the "Log In" button to log in.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Other possible explanations:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
1. If you copied and pasted the URL from
your confirmation email, please make sure you did so correctly and
completely.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
2. If you received this confirmation email a long time ago
and never confirmed your account, it is possible that your account has
been purged from the system. In that case, you should simply apply
for a new account.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Il codice di conferma non è valido.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Questo forse perchè tu hai già confermto l'account. Se è così, per loggarsi basta cliccare sul pulsante "Log In".
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Altre possibili spiegazioni:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
1. Se tu hai copiato ed incollato l'URL dalla mail di conferma, prego assicurati di averlo fatto correttamente e completamente.
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
2. Se tu hai ricevuto la mail di conferma molto tempo fa e non l'hai mai confermta, è possibile che il tuo account sia stato cancellato dal sistema.
In questo caso, tu devi procedere semplicemente registrandoti di nuovo.
&lt;/p&gt;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="4" approved="yes">
        <source>Apply for an Account</source>
        <target>Crea un Account</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="5" approved="yes">
        <source>Create My Account</source>
        <target>Crea il Mio Account</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="6" approved="yes">
        <source>or</source>
        <target>oppure</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="7" approved="yes">
        <source>Cancel</source>
        <target>Annulla</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="8" approved="yes">
        <source>Forgot your username or password? No problem! Just enter your username &lt;strong&gt;or&lt;/strong&gt;
your email address and click "Reset My Password." You will receive an email message containing both your username and
a link permitting you to change your password if you wish.</source>
        <target>Hai dimenticato la tua username o password? Nessun problema! Basta digitare la propria username &lt;strong&gt;o&lt;/strong&gt;
o il proprio indirizzo email e cliccare "Resetta la Mia Password.". Tu riceverai un messagio mail contenente lo username e
un link che ti permetterà di cambiare la tua password se tu lo desideri.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="9" approved="yes">
        <source>Reset My Password</source>
        <target>Resetta la Mia Password</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="10" approved="yes">
        <source>Thanks for applying for an account with %1%.

To prevent abuse of the site, we require that you activate your account by clicking on the following link:

%2%

Thanks again for joining us.</source>
        <target>
Grazie per aver registrato un account con %1%.

Per prevenire abusi sul sito, noi richiediamo che tu attivi il tuo account cliccando sul seguente link:

%2%

Grazie ancora per esserti registrato.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="11" approved="yes">
        <source>Your password has been successfully reset. You are now logged
in to this site. In the future, be sure to log in with your new password.</source>
        <target>La tua password è stata resettata con successo. Ora tu sei loggato nel sito. In futuro, assicurati di loggarti con una nuova password.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="12" approved="yes">
        <source>Thanks for confirming your email address. You may now change your
password using the form below.</source>
        <target>Grazie per aver confermato il tuo indirizzo email. Ora tu poi cambiare la tua password usando il form sottostante.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="13" approved="yes">
        <source>&lt;p&gt;
For security reasons, a confirmation message has been sent to 
the email address associated with this account. Please check your
email for that message. You will need to click on a link provided
in that email in order to change your password. If you do not see
the message, be sure to check your "spam" and "bulk" email folders.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
We apologize for the inconvenience.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Per ragioni di sicurezza, un messaggio di conferma è stato inviato all'indirizzo email associato a questo account. Prego, controlla la tua casella di posta elettronica.
Tu dovrai cliccare sul link fornito nella mail per cambiare la password. Se non vedi il messaggio, assicurati di controllare le tue cartelle "spam" e "bulk".
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Ci scusiamo per l'inconveniente.
&lt;/p&gt;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="14" approved="yes">
        <source>
&lt;p&gt;
We have received your request to recover your username and possibly your password on: %1%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Your username is: %USERNAME%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
If you have lost your password or wish to reset it, click on the link that follows:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
%2%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
You will then be prompted for the new password you wish to use.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Your password will not be changed unless you click on the link above and complete the form.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Noi abbiamo ricevuto la tua richiesta di recupero per lo username e possibilmente la tua password su: %1%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Il tuo username è: %USERNAME%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Se hai perso la tua password o desideri resettarla, clicca sul seguente link:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
%2%
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Facendolo, ti verrà data la possibilità di immettere la nuova password che tu desidererai usare.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
La tua password non sarà cambiata a meno che tu non clicchi su link sopra e completi il form.
&lt;/p&gt;
</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="15" approved="yes">
        <source>&lt;p&gt;
An error took place during the email delivery process. Please try
again later.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Un errore è avvenuto durante l'invio della mail. Prego ritentare fra poco.
&lt;/p&gt;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="16" approved="yes">
        <source>sign in</source>
        <target>login</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="17" approved="yes">
        <source>Reset Your Password</source>
        <target>Resetta la Tua Password</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="18" approved="yes">
        <source>Create a New Account</source>
        <target>Crea un Nuovo Account</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="19" approved="yes">
        <source>Account Settings</source>
        <target>Settaggi Account</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="20" approved="yes">
        <source>Save</source>
        <target>Salva</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="21" approved="yes">
        <source>Click the button below to change your password.</source>
        <target>Clicca il pulsante in basso per cambiare la tua password.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="22" approved="yes">
        <source>Reset Password</source>
        <target>Resetta Password</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="23" approved="yes">
        <source>Thank you for applying for an account. You will receive a verification
email shortly. If you do not see that email, please be sure to check your "spam" or "bulk" folder.</source>
        <target>Grazie per aver richiesto un account. A breve
riceverai un'email di conferma. Se non la vedi controlla la cartella
"spam" o "bulk".
</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="24" approved="yes">
        <source>Sorry, there is no user with that username or email address.</source>
        <target>Scusa, non esiste alcun utente con questo username o indirizzo email.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="25" approved="yes">
        <source>
That account was never verified. You must verify the account before you can log in or, if
necessary, reset the password. We have resent your verification email, which contains
instructions to verify your account. If you do not see that email, please be sure to check 
your "spam" or "bulk" folder.</source>
        <target>Questo account non è stato mai confermato. Tu devi confermare l'accont prima di loggarti o, se necessari, resettare la password.
        Noi ti abbiamo reinviato la mail di conferma, che contiene azioni per confermare il tuo account. Se tu non vedi la mail, prego assicurati di controllare la cartella "spam" o "bulk".
</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="26" approved="yes">
        <source>We have received your request to recover your username and possibly your password on:

%1%

Your username is: %USERNAME%

If you have lost your password or wish to reset it, click on the link that follows:

%2%

You will then be prompted for the new password you wish to use.

Your password will NOT be changed unless you click on the link above and complete the form.</source>
        <target>Abbiamo ricevuto la tua richiesta per recuperare il tuo username e possibilmente la tua password su:

%1%

Il tuo username è : %USERNAME%

Se tu hai perso la tua password o desideri resettarla clicca sul seguente link:

%2%

Verrai reindirizzato sulla modifica della nuova password che tu desideri usare.
La tua password non sarba cambiata fintanto che tu non clicchi sul link e completi il form.
</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="27" approved="yes">
        <source>Thank you for confirming your account! You are now logged into the site.</source>
        <target>Grazie per aver confermato il tuo account! Ora tu sei loggato nel sito.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="28" approved="yes">
        <source>&lt;p&gt;
This account is inactive. Please contact the administrator.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;
Questo account è inattivo. Prego, contattare l'amministratore.
&lt;/p&gt;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="29" approved="yes">
        <source>Logged in as %1%</source>
        <target>Loggato come %1%</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="30" approved="yes">
        <source>Log Out</source>
        <target>Log Out</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="31" approved="yes">
        <source>Settings</source>
        <target>Settaggi</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="32" approved="yes">
        <source>Please verify your account on %1%</source>
        <target>Prego, verifica il tuo account su %1%</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="33" approved="yes">
        <source>Please verify your password reset request on %1%</source>
        <target>Prego, verifica la tua richiesta di reset password su %1%</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="34" approved="yes">
        <source>You may change your password using the form below.</source>
        <target>Puoi cambiare la tua password usando il seguente form.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="35" approved="yes">
        <source>The captcha is not valid (%error%).</source>
        <target>Il Captcha non e' valido (%error%).</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="36" approved="yes">
        <source>Unable to check the captcha from the server (%error%).</source>
        <target>Non possiamo verificare il captcha dal server (%error%).</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit id="43" approved="yes">
        <source>For security reasons, you
will receive a confirmation email containing a link allowing you to complete the password change.</source>
        <target>Per motivi di sicurezza, riceverai una mail di conferma contenente un link che ti permettera' di completare il cambio della password.</target>
      </trans-unit>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>
